# **Abhijeet Singh**

### Software Developer | abjt.dev

I build engaging experiences for my audience with pixel-perfect and performant applications. With a creative approach to development, I add intuitiveness and life to my work.

I am a big-time musicophile with a passion for art and human psychology. My latest endeavour has been building 3d artwork using Blender.



+1 604 339 8625



abhijeetsinghmain@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/abjt14



github.com/abjt14

## **Experience**

#### AvenueHQ

Junior Full-Stack Engineer | Mar 2022 - Present

- · Working on a digital marketing tool for realtors through North America.
- · Building a performant client facing API-driven application in React.
- · Using Laravel and SQL to build fast, efficient and scalable databases and APIs.
- Collaborating across internal teams to clarify requirements, explore issues, provide updates, and present discoveries.

#### Outlined.co

Software Engineer | Sept 2019 - Oct 2020

- Developed and maintained the company's product marketing website and flagship design platform using FabricIS and Laravel.
- · Built a PDF to HTML canvas converter using JavaScript and Shell Scripting to import and export designs on the browser.
- Implemented API Integration for data storage, social media interaction, text sentimental analysis, and stock image services.

#### Education

#### Langara College | Vancouver, BC, Canada

Post-Graduate Diploma | 2020-2022 Web and Mobile App Design and Development

#### Manipal University Jaipur | Jaipur, Rajasthan, India

Backend

Nuxt

NodelS

Laravel

• MySQL

MongoDB

GraphQL

Bachelor In Technology | 2015-2019 Information Technology

#### **Technical Skills**

Technologies, tools, and utilities I've recently used in personal, educational, and professional projects.

I enjoy wearing multiple hats in a project, working with different cogs of the machine that we call a product.

#### Frontend

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Svelte
- ReactIS
- React Native
- Vue
- Sass
- Less
- GSAP

#### **Tools and Utilities**

- Shell Scripting
- Git
- Github
- npm
- yarn
- Figma